My friend, my bike actually got
rejected, let me tell you
what all has been rejected in it, that
brother Gandh hit a truck, what kind of
accident happened in it, such an accident happened, you
know something was parked,
Jhala Jhala is an
army vehicle, there is a
man left, it happened, it happened
to Ajay, come back
to my YouTube channel, guys, today
I am going to take delivery of my bike, many
people would know, many
people would not know, my bike had met with an
accident due to which
I was not able to make a video with proper, so it took
10 to 15 days for
my bike to be completed, I
also got a call from Kalp company that the radio
jockey can come and take your bike, so now you
know what all the company Weston had, I
also had a lot of lessons, that has been digitized,
so let's see what the result is, so
now you will get the motor clock
setup directly, so friend, we have left,
sitting on the Splendor and  Quickly solve the
problem and today it is very cold in Patna, I
mean great people, it has reached Manali and it is just about to
snow, the
temperature will be 9 to 10 degrees,
due to the full hand not being available, the full
hand is inclined, that is,
ghee is sitting, so I will go now, then
after that it will have to be brought on the bike, so that is why
I have taken it, so
friends, today I will show you how much
my insurance was caught by the
gang and how much processing is this, the
processing speed, how much did I have to do,
everything, what was
rejected for me and for how much I
got it,
you will know all this by the end of this video and how much was the
bill, everything, so let's quickly go to the
showroom and I will try to keep this video
as short as possible, I will talk point to point,
if friends, you
want some video related to this bike, then
definitely tell me in the comment box what should I make of it,
if you want to see a video of
Splendor, then friends, if you have
not seen my previous video,
how to reduce the insurance, what documents have to be sent and
submitted, everything, then that video will be
coming up on the i button, so  Please go and see if it is
processed through MP4, does it take so much time, do I have to
submit any documents,
you will get to see all this in this video,
in this video I will just
show you what the cost was, how much did I have to pay, what all,
my claim was
rejected, so let's quickly go to the
showroom,
yes friend, I would like to tell you one more thing, if
you go to take delivery of a claim like yours, then make a thorough
inspection that is the bike coming, you mean is there any problem in the meantime, etc., then
delivery is done only after checking everything, check your two drops etc.,
whatever is there, do all this, it is
necessary to do all this, nothing like this happens, but do it
for your satisfaction and also
check in the bike, what all has been
changed, that part, everything,
check it, once the change has happened, it takes
time for you to repair it, I am just
telling you that this keeps happening, I am
not saying that everyone does it, but if it happens, then turn it on and
start  It's a very busy bike,
which one is in the name of Congress Bahu Kumar, it does
n't have an award on it, it does
n't have an hourglass, there are rubber bands on the
handle, there's a
mudguard,
ok, I forgot what was changed,
brother, the truck driver killed it, did a
robber get it, if it's not there, then you seem to get it
installed,
why not the old one, his name is
Ajay,
I came from this company,
yes, it is, it must be
installed on it too, if it is
not there, then he
asked, what kind of accident happened, you
know, something has been parked, it's an
army vehicle, there is a
man left,
so let's make the payment quickly,
why have you put it here for years, the hair is the
bell, it's stained, so I'll show you
how much it can be put,
open the battery, there's something, this is the
tool box,
and look here, put the scratches, let's put this crush on it,
ok brother,
I'm not an expert in installing it, I
hope it will be rejected, so
now we're going to go for a ride, I hope
you all don't have an accident, so
let's finally friends, so many days  After this, I am having this
bike in my hand after a long time and I am
feeling good riding it and I hope that everything is
fine now, first I will take it and install it, now I will
come quickly in it, so now the
Bhor Tara video is going to be
related to it, right now first I will go and
teach you everything about the bill etc. so
stop somewhere on the side and see what else to do, the text has
also changed and how much I have to pay,
I will tell you everything, so now
friends, do watch the video till the end, so now let's go as soon as possible, the
silencer of this Honda CB that is going in front has been changed and a joint account has been good, I will
hear from you guys if you ask me, I will tell you, it is
good, by the way, its sound, its seat does
not look that good, its WhatsApp is coming out good,
now we will talk about the part changes that
I have, the one that was changed was this
handlebar and this front
Brett Lee and whatever is there is changed and let me
show you for a second, just
look at this cover, the one on top has been changed and this has also
changed and this panel  Yes, it was completely
changed and this back lever that you see at the
back, that of Brett Lee, and this entire road was changed
and this has also been changed, the footrest
and the front headlight were changed and now let's talk about
what the cost was, let me tell you, let's
talk about the take care claim was
rejected, so this chilli was
rejected, there are a few scratches here
and here also it must be somewhere below, it is
not visible on the side and this pimple and I got it
repaired, it has gone to the side due to which
only scratches were visible, now you can see,
this is my result, this
comes for Shlok 26 for something, so this support has
gone in the marriage act,
now let's talk about how much cost
I had to pay, so let us show what
cost I incurred, well,
this is Rs. 5745, its total cost, so
friends, the company paid this much in this and I had to pay this much
amount, so
I had to pay a total of 100 rupees
and the insurance company paid the fee
and my total claim was, so I
just  100 feet back and stomach, friends,
my total cost in this was
5700, something story, Hanuman's feet, 5800
use and many videos related to modification are
also going to come, friends, so please
come and subscribe to the channel, thank you
for watching my video.